meditation number 15 and 16 I repeated
it I repeated a picture in both
meditations what's the picture the two
husband's okay this is what we call a
DCI life tool there are 96 DCI life
tools okay once you know them you're
really smart okay this is one of them is
called the two husbands all right does
the lady look happy no why
the husband is yelling at her what does
it mean I wink it do it up here I don't
know we should do it huh well Nick's
really good at it shoppings good at it
you come come quick be the husband I'm
the wife you're one of the husbands okay
these are my three bad kids right here
okay
I'm the wife you know I'm a working
woman okay so I have three naughty kids
she's almost real life and and then I
have a husband okay
then I'm working full-time because the
husband likes to watch soccer and he's
not interested in so anyway my life is
like that five days a week I take my
kids to school before I go to work and
then I work for eight or ten hours if I
live in Guangzhou I probably work for 14
hours and then I come home but on the
way home I have to buy groceries because
my husband's watching soccer
not penny of course but uh so they when
I come home I'm really really tired okay
exhausting so you know the story because
that's your real life now on on Tuesday
afternoon my boss tells me that on
Wednesday morning I have to come in
early probably because we have a Skype
call with the Vasek in America and we
live in China so I don't know why they
can't have a Skype call in the middle of
night it's always in Chinese you have to
have the Skype call me mellow night and
my boss told me don't forget you have to
come I want you here at 8 o'clock in the
morning not 9 o'clock okay so then
Tuesday night I have to tell my three
kids you know tomorrow mommy has to go
to work early and you know so I want you
to be dressed for school not at not at
seven o'clock but like 6:30 okay and
have you homework finished and be
dressed and have your shoes on and
everything and then mommy's got to take
you to school earlier because mommy has
to work okay then they promise see how
they're nodding and then then next
morning when mommy walked in the room
dad jumping on the bed you don't have to
stand jumping on the bed
they don't have their school clothes
bombs they lost their shoes nobody can
find them they're under the bed
someplace then mommy's like I told you
to be ready I mean I am so stupid
your honor stupidest kitty poncho you
know like that okay then mommy who heard
mommy yeah the three kids maybe they
heard me they didn't but mommy here's
mommy
okay when mommy here's mommy say bad
thing mommy makes a bad seed that plant
a bad seed in mommy's mind okay next
week Monday bad day right
Monday's always the worst day so you go
to word you had a long day you took the
kids to school you went to learn your
boss kept you late I'll tell your
interesting thing about bosses they give
you so much trouble if you show up late
in the morning but they don't they're
not shy to ask you to stay late in the
afternoon well why is that
my boss he starts screaming at me you
know you're late you're ten minutes late
I say you kept me three hours late
yesterday I'm 10 minutes late you kept
me to Mijares late you know they think
they don't understand you know so he
keeps me late then I come home sorry I
went to buy groceries because my husband
is watching a football game soccer game
then I'm tired you know then I come home
and all I want the reason I have a
husband the only reason because he
doesn't work much is to give me hugs you
know I like to have some that feeling of
him hugging me you know that's why I
keep him you know and then I'm looking
forward to having a hug you ready come
home late open the door I'm home
fun phone and just then the husband call
you
rice bucketheads because you're late
right the husband is upset because
husband didn't get dinner during the
soccer game
okay then they call you stupid all right
now normal the normal reaction is what
no roof on tone no neat new font on your
frontal you know I'm not I'm not rice
bucket head you're right head
okay like that okay that's normal
reaction okay what happens if you do
then who hears it you hear it plants
another seed next week he will do again
okay
because he's coming from you okay he's
like a pin he's coming from you okay why
did he yell are you yeah because you
planted a seed last week last Wednesday
you planted see okay he's coming from
you
whose fault yeah it's you fault okay now
bad news every irritating person you
ever met
what's coming from you everyone most
people want to say good luck 90% of
people I meet who are irritating coming
from me but my ex-husband he's not
coming from me he's so bad okay keep up
things out it's really a hundred percent
okay it's really a hundred percent so if
you so this husband called jumping okay
I I believe not coming from me not my
fault you can take a deep breath
and you could say in one word I didn't
do anything I didn't do anything I just
opened the door I didn't do anything and
then he called me phantom I all I'm
always okay that that husband not my
fault that husband not my fault does it
exist or not doesn't exist okay that
husband we call in buddhism in tibetan
we call it who said gotcha nice okay
that's a self existent thing that's
that's a gotcha that's the thing that's
not there and that's the meaning of
illusion okay it looks like he's there
but it's not there that's Maya that's
illusion okay don't don't get all
mystical on me okay it's not mystical
it's all about husband's okay okay that
that husband is Maya that husband
appears to be real and doesn't exist the
husband who's not I didn't do anything
so much fun that husband doesn't exist
never existed will never exist cannot
exist okay because it's not coming from
you that's impossible
that's the impossible husband now the
other husband Nick the lousy husband
right now that one is my fault
that one I created last week with my
three bad kids
okay I planted a seed by hearing my own
thing right and a planet seed next week
the seat opens picture comes out goes on
top of Nick's body and mind okay
that's dependent origination if you want
to use stupid long Buddhist words okay
Syd come out see it open up dependent
origination let's just call come from my
seeds same thing
okay he comes from me okay
does that husband exist yeah he's
dependent origination okay
she's emptiness okay they go together
okay she doesn't exist
that one isn't there that's emptiness
okay the the absence of this husband in
the universe
it's called emptiness okay the presence
of this husband who comes from my seats
is called dependent origination every
time you meet anybody until you are
eighth level buddy suffered there will
be two of them in the room there will
always be two of them in the room okay
there's always two husbands in your room
in your kitchen always okay always
because your mind is still making this
sauce sake once but you know that it's
not true there's two husbands in the
room all the time now big big big big
big big big big question when you get
upset and you want to say now I'm not
stupid you're stupid okay when you're so
stupid you are stupid by planting a new
seed okay but so now you Steven okay
when you get upset when you get angry
which husband are you angry at chopping
or Nick yeah shall be analysis okay so
learn something understand something
every time you got upset or nervous or
frightened or worried in your whole life
you are worried or angry or frightened
about something that wasn't there and
all war in this world world world war
two killed a hundred million people
thirty five million in China
okay from Japan right that killed a
hundred million people those enemies
didn't exist okay
hundred million people died being hating
someone who wasn't Gareth but it killed
100 million people I said I mean it's
amazing it's it's incredible
okay got it now what happened what do we
call it if you say oh you I understand
where you come from it's because I yell
at my kids last week you know I won't do
that again okay what's that called when
you use emptiness to stop your anger
what's that call nirvana
it's called nirvana that's the
definition under bummer
okay I will not get angry because I know
I will plant another things then you
stop the cycle that's called you broke
the wheel of life okay you broke some
sorry okay cool